[theme music playing]
[Jaguar] It's just the start.
We'll take all of the Ardientes' money.
We'll milk them dry.
-[man 1] For the Jaguar!
-[other men] Jaguar!
[Julio] An armed group of men
broke into our gambling den.
And the leader of this group
calls himself Jaguar.
Miss Camia, you don't know how happy
you're going to make me
if you let me work for you!
-All right.
-Thank you, Miss Camia!
[Arnaldo] A lifetime
of love and happiness.
Ivy Aguas, will you marry me?
[Ivy] Yes, Arnaldo. I will marry you.
How will I bring the Ardientes down?
Step one: make their favorite
grandson fall for me,
and use him against them.
Achievement unlocked.
[man] Jaguar. The boss is here…
[Natalie] Mr. Jaguar?
What a cool name.
[Nimfa] I think I've earned her trust.
Don't worry, Governor.
We'll learn all of Camia Cruz's secrets.
Even who her backer is.
[Emilia] I already know it's Ivy Aguas.
[Diego] Is it true?
Are you going to marry Arnaldo?
Yes.
[Diego] You're going to marry the man
who might've killed Nanny Carlotta?
I'm sorry, Ivy. But I'd do anything
to stop you from marrying Arnaldo!
I'm sorry.
I just love you too much.
[ominous music playing]
[line rings]
Is she all right?
Why isn't she picking up?
Miss Camia, I brought you tea.
I wanted to apologize
for what happened earlier.
Don't worry about it, Nimfa.
Just don't do it again, okay?
Yes.
[sighs]
You can't make a call?
I noticed that there's no reception here.
I can go with you outside
so you can call whoever it is
you're trying to reach.
No, it's fine.
I'm going to take a shower,
then I'm off to bed.
You should head home.
Have the driver drop you off.
-Okay.
-You can leave that there.
Okay.
[ominous music playing]
Oh! It spilled!
-I'm sorry! I spilled the tea!
-What happened?
I spilled the tea.
Don't worry, ma'am.
I'll take care of this.
I'll get this fixed
by the time you're done.
I'm so sorry.
-Okay.
-Oh, my.
[ominous music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
[line rings]
[ringing continues]
[suspenseful music continues]
Nimfa!
Who's on the phone?
Oh! Miss Camia.
What are you doing with my phone?
And why did you answer that call?
Uh… I thought it was someone important.
Someone named "A" was calling.
Who is that?
Nimfa, just go home.
And don't touch my phone next time, okay?
Go on.
[tense music playing]
[door closes]
-Hello, dear.
-Mom?
I'm sorry, dear.
Nimfa got a hold of my phone.
I heard! Why was she
going through your stuff?
Mom, I know we've known her for a while,
but we can't just trust her.
It's risky.
We can't just trust…
the people around us.
Is that why you've become particular
with our bodyguards too?
Yes, Mom!
Because our former bodyguards
couldn't even protect Nanny Carlotta!
If something bad happens…
I know I can protect myself.
But you, Mom…
I want you to be extra careful. Please.
Even from people like Nimfa.
Please.
Okay, dear. I'll be careful.
And I'll try to get to know her more.
Yes, Mom. Please.
Okay, bye.
[unsettling music playing]
[ominous music playing]
-Give it to them.
-Yes, Boss.
You're the best, Mr. Jaguar!
Thanks for this!
-Thanks, sir!
Thanks, sir!
There's more where that came from.
If you do your jobs properly
and remain loyal to me,
I guarantee, you'll all be
swimming in a pool of money.
You can count on us, Mr. Jaguar.
Right, boys?
Cheers, boys!
Cheers!
[tense music playing]
[Arnaldo] I want everyone
to be present at dinner.
This is very important to me.
I think I know what this is about.
But don't worry.
I won't preempt you.
[Julio] Oh, and by the way…
Don't expect your father
to be there tomorrow.
Well, I don't really care
about him, so it's fine.
No, since you're requiring
everyone to be present,
I'll make sure your father's there.
I'll invite him. He'll be there.
[chuckles]
I wonder whose bed Raul
is sleeping on right now.
Emilia,
I bet your husband's sleeping
with yet another woman.
Papa, believe it or not, Raul has changed.
-What?
-Yes, Papa!
In fact, he actually wants us
to renew our vows.
[laughs sarcastically]
[Julio and Arnaldo laughing]
That's the dumbest idea I've heard
since "women empowerment."
Do you seriously still believe Raul?
He's been feeding you nothing but lies,
and yet here you are,
crazy enough to believe
his empty promises!
I just don't get it!
[ominous music playing]
I'm sure Emilia's going to like this.
I just know she won't suspect anything…
when I give this to her.
Well, I have a better idea.
What if…
you choke your wife with this necklace?
Choke her until her eyes pop out.
[grunts]
[laughs]
What do you think?
Well, Raul…
I can't keep waiting.
I want to rip Emilia's face apart
and bury her alive.
[ominous music playing]
Just wait a little more, Natalie.
Once we get all the Ardientes' wealth,
including their illegal properties,
we will take control of everything.
I will be the king…
and you will be my queen.
I trust you.
But my impatience
may get the better of me.
So, be fast.
You shouldn't keep me waiting.
[tense music playing]
[groans]
-Emilia, hello.
-Where have you been?
Didn't I mention--
I just noticed, Raul,
you always keep me waiting here.
-Where have you been?
-I told you…
I'd just check on my business.
Liar!
No, Emilia. What?
Do I smell like a baby?
Well?
Give me your phone.
-I don't understand--
-Give it to me!
What's wrong with you, Emilia?
What now? Go on, check all of it.
Did you find something?
Are you done now?
Now, it's my turn.
Let me do this.
You know, Emilia…
when I told you I would change,
I meant it.
Well, I don't believe
any single word that you say.
I know you're just fooling me.
Wait.
[unsettling music playing]
[exhales]
I have something for you.
Maybe by giving this to you,
you won't get mad at me anymore.
Hmm?
That's the business I was talking about.
We have diamonds and jewelry.
Come on, smile!
You even tried to smell me, huh?
[chuckles]
Where's my phone?
-Wait. See? I knew it!
-[phone rings]
Is this your new mistress?!
-I told you, I'm right.
-Emilia…
Raul, I have a suggestion for you.
Since you want to have a new business,
why don't you put up a funeral home?
You know why? You'll earn a lot more.
Because I'll have
all your mistresses killed!
Give me that, I need to answer--
Wait!
Hello?
Yes.
This is Governor Emilia Ardiente-Torillo.
The wife of Raul.
This is to inform you
that I've already scheduled your funeral.
See you!
[unsettling music playing]
Give me that!
Do you know who that was?
That was my boss.
He's the one doing business with me.
With all the diamonds and jewelry.
How can I succeed if you don't
trust me in the first place?
Didn't I tell you
I'd change for the better?
Emilia…
How many times do I need
to tell you I love you?
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
[deep sigh]
[Arnaldo] Go on, just put it there.
-What's that?
-Before she comes down.
-Get the rest inside too.
-Arnaldo?
What's this? What's happening?
Good morning!
Good morning, but what's happening?
Well, I hired some new maids for you.
Just to help you maintain this house
since Carlotta's gone.
[tense music playing]
[groans]
Hon, thank you.
I appreciate it.
But I don't need new maids.
I can manage here alone.
No, you don't have to do that.
Why not?
Wait.
Do you think that ruthless
murderer will come back here?
Well, hon, let me tell you this.
I'm not afraid to face them.
Because with all the knives I have here,
I can return the favor.
I'm not afraid of them!
[tense music playing]
Hey, hon.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Uh…
I was just thinking…
maybe…
you don't need to be alone.
So, after our wedding,
I'd like you to move in
with me into the mansion.
I'd love that! But, the question is…
Will Emilia be okay
with me being the new queen
of the Ardientes' mansion?
Well, like I said,
no one cares what she thinks.
And she's no longer queen.
You are.
Aw, hon!
Thank you.
You are such a sweet fiancé.
Come here.
Okay. Let's eat.
Oops! You sit here.
You aren't my husband yet,
but soon, you will be.
[laughs]
Okay.
Aww, thank you, hon.
Do you want juice or coffee?
Yeah.
Well, hon, you have to bring
your maids with you.
You need to follow the queen's orders.
Or else, there won't be a wedding.
[sighs]
I love you.
Well, I love you more.
[chuckles]
Aunt Camia, let's push through
with the case.
Arthur and I can testify
against the Ardientes.
I'll spill all their dirt!
Diego, hold on.
Let's not be too impulsive.
What's going on?
Why are you acting like this?
It's about Ivy.
[unsettling music playing]
She's getting married to Arnaldo.
We can't let that happen.
Aunt Camia, we have to stop Ivy.
[tense music playing]
It's pretty…
and full of crap.
Aunt Claire, stop being so negative.
-Wasn't this sweet of Raul?
-[scoffs]
Manipulating.
Focus on your goal, Emilia!
Bring Camia Cruz down,
so you can earn Julio's approval.
I haven't forgotten
about that, Aunt Claire.
Really?
How's our mole in Camia's camp doing?
Does she have any new information?
See?
You're taking too long, Emilia!
I'm getting worried.
I'm sure Camia's starting
to suspect that girl.
She wouldn't do such a thing
without a plan in mind.
Let's just trust her.
Don't worry.
I'll talk to her.
I'll ask her about her plan.
I'll tell you everything.
Oh.
I prepared some drinks and snacks.
Go ahead and eat.
[tense music playing]
Um, I'll head back inside.
-[Camia sighs]
-Aunt Camia, what's wrong?
Diego.
How well do you know Nimfa?
Can we really trust her?
Nimfa and I grew up together.
I don't see any reason
why we shouldn't trust her.
Why? Did something happen?
Did she do something?
I'm sorry. I guess I'm just
being paranoid, Diego.
[phone ringing]
Speaking of the bitch, Aunt Claire.
Hello, Nimfa?
Well? I hope you have good news for us.
[suspenseful music playing]
So?
What is it?
Ivy and Arnaldo are now engaged.
Oh, my.
So, this is what the dinner
is all about, Aunt Claire.
[laughs]
Great.
Ivy had better watch out.
I have a plan, and she'll
regret saying yes to my son.
[tense music playing]
[water running]
Nimfa.
Diego.
How are you doing here?
I'm doing well.
Miss Camia is kind.
Even though I get a bit nosy.
Did she tell you about what I did?
I'm really embarrassed.
I'm so sorry, Diego.
Don't worry. It's nothing.
You know I trust you, right?
So, I hope you won't do anything
that'll ruin our friendship.
[tense music playing]
Okay. I have to go.
Take care.
Uh, Diego!
You look troubled.
I'm sorry again.
I overheard your conversation
with Miss Camia.
So, Miss Ivy and Mayor Arnaldo
are engaged.
If you ever need someone
to talk to, I'm here.
Oh, I have something to get from my house.
Can you come with me?
Let it out. It's not good to keep it in.
Nimfa, I'm fine.
You wouldn't let me
walk home alone, right?
Especially this late.
Diego.
Why do you let Ivy Aguas
affect you so much?
Don't you ever think there's someone else
who's better for you?
A girl who can really love you.
A girl who won't lead you on
like what Ivy's doing to you.
[unsettling music playing]
A girl who can give you everything…
and who'll do everything for you.
Diego.
Just say the word, and I'll be that girl.
[unsettling music playing]
Nimfa, wait.
We're just friends.
Can we not ruin what we have?
[car door opens]
Nimfa, go home.
[tense music playing]
[Claire] This is really good, right?
[Julio] Yeah.
Well, it's supposed to be
a special dinner because…
Arnaldo.
We've had a good meal.
Now, you said you were going to have
an announcement to make?
Yes, Grandpa. I have
an announcement to make.
Rather, we have an announcement to make.
[suspenseful music playing]
Go on.
But before you make that announcement,
I have a surprise for both of you.
Hold on.
[Emilia] Jenny! Jenny!
Please, bring it out.
I didn't see this coming.
A cake?
Surprise!
Congratulations on your engagement, Ivy.
[tense music playing]
How thoughtful of you, Emilia.
But where's the bride's head?
[chuckles]
Isn't it obvious, Ivy?
It's obvious you don't
like me for Arnaldo,
that's why you'll do everything
to get in the way of our relationship.
Yes. Oh, wait.
That's exactly what I wanted to say.
[Julio] Emilia.
-It's okay, Congressman.
-I'm so sorry.
No. It's okay, hon.
But I guess I need to go home, Arnaldo.
I'm not welcome in this house.
-And we're done.
-Excuse me. Excuse me.
Oh, wait. Let me escort you out.
Because aside from my son,
you might end up seducing our guards too.
Emilia, please.
It's okay.
Excuse me.
Emilia, I said excuse me.
[tense music playing]
-[grunts]
-[shrieks]
-Stop it!
-Emilia.
You can cross anyone but not me!
-Stop it.
-Stop them!
You're really getting on my nerves!
-Ivy, that's enough!
-Stop it, Ivy!
-Stop it! Stop it!
-Ivy! That's enough!
-Don't try to stop me!
-Mom!
Arnaldo, take Ivy away from here.
I said stop it!
-Arnaldo!
-Please, that's enough!
The two of you! Stop it!
You want to chop my head off?
Not if I chop yours first!
Enough, enough, enough! Ivy.
Come here. Please.
Please!
Don't try me, Emilia.
Not me!
-The both of you, stop it!
-We aren't done yet!
Remember this!
I'm gonna do everything
to ruin your engagement with my son!
Bring it on!
-Arnaldo, take Ivy outside!
-Let me go!
Get out of my house!
I won't leave
because I will be the
new queen of this mansion.
[Emilia laughing]
[Julio] Is this really
the future of this family?
Look at you!
Supposed educated women of the society.
Look how you're acting!
You're worse than animals in a jungle!
I have seen women of ill repute
behave better than the two of you!
You're worse than prostitutes
getting at each other's throats!
A classic example of a lowlife catfight!
Is this the future of my life?
For me to have a daughter who is a bitch,
and another bitch for a daughter-in-law?!
Dirty doesn't even come close
to what you've shown here tonight!
Shame on you!
Shame on both of you!
Animals!
I never thought I'd see the day.
[tense music playing]
[Emilia groans]
Thank you, hon. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
You know, your mom…
-I know. I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry, hon.
I didn't mean to do it. [sobbing]
You saw what she did, right?
-Yes.
-She started it.
I know. It's not your fault. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Arnaldo.
I didn't want this to happen.
Congressman, I'm sorry.
[tense music playing]
Stop crying, hon.
[sobbing]
[fakes sobbing]
Oh, that woman! I swear!
You know what, Emilia? You shouldn't have
insulted her in the first place.
Look what happened to you.
So, how's the cake?
Oh, quit it. I'll kill that woman!
Calm down, Emilia!
Think about the repercussions
of what you did!
Julio will be mad at you.
[Claire] Arnaldo is the golden boy.
And you, Emilia…
of all the Ardientes I know,
you're the one who never learned anything
from what I've taught you!
-Papa…
-You know why?
You always act before you think!
What's wrong with you?
I just don't trust that woman!
Neither do I!
I don't trust her.
But, did I ever show her that?
Of course not. Why?
Because we need her.
How many times do I have
to tell you all that?
Or do I have to hit you with this
so you finally learn your lesson?
Emilia!
[groans]
[tense music playing]
[Julio] Your head's up your butt!
I'll make sure to uncover
that woman's dirt!
Especially now.
She better watch her back.
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
[sighs]
[deep sigh]
-Here.
-I'm still shaking.
Hon, I'll be fine. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, hon.
Um…
I think it'd be better if I just go home.
I don't really feel that
I'm welcome in this house.
Please? I need to go home.
No. You're not going home, okay?
Stay here for the night.
Hon.
[sighs]
This is just so painful.
My heart's still racing, hon.
How did this even happen?
It's just embarrassing. I don't want this.
I don't want to fight with
my future mother-in-law.
I guess, Emilia and I
will never get along, so…
Let's just call off the wedding.
Maybe we aren't meant
for each other, Arnaldo.
No, no. Hey! That's nonsense, okay?
Hon.
No. Don't ever think about that.
No one else deserves my love, but you.
No other woman deserves me, but you.
Don't ever think that way.
Oh, hon.
You know what?
I… I really think Mom's just insecure
because she will never be as
powerful and as wealthy
as you are.
That's why she's always targeting you.
Of course not.
Your mom is an ex-governor,
and she's an Ardiente.
That means she's wealthy.
Well, our family is rich, but she isn't.
What?
You mean…
Emilia doesn't have her own money?
[scoffs]
She doesn't.
Besides, she doesn't know where
Grandpa's keeping our money.
Overseas accounts?
Overseas accounts, as you already know,
are hard to maintain,
so we prefer it nearby
and easily accessible.
Hon, aren't you afraid
the banks will be able
to trace all your wealth?
That's risky.
Who said our money's in the bank?
We prefer stacking it in piles
and counting it by millions.
Good idea.
-I'm still shaking.
-Have some water.
-I'm really sorry, hon.
-No. Stop saying sorry.
It's not your fault.
I didn't mean to hurt your mother.
You know how much I love you, right?
-I know.
-I love you, hon.
-I love you.
[unsettling music playing]
[ominous music playing]
Ivy will stay here tonight.
I asked her to stay
because something might happen
to her on her way home.
Oh, and by the way,
this will be the last time
you'll disrespect her.
Apologize to her.
Over my dead body, Arnaldo!
I will not apologize to her!
She started everything
when she smashed a cake--
Enough!
I'm sick and tired of
hearing all your nonsense.
That woman will soon be my wife
and the future mother of my children.
Apologize to her…
or else you're going to lose a son…
and gain one more enemy on your list.
This is unbelievable, Arnaldo!
You are unbelievable!
[tense music playing]
[Arnaldo] Overseas accounts,
as you already know,
are hard to maintain.
So, we prefer it nearby
and easily accessible.
Aren't you afraid the banks will be able
to trace all your wealth?
Who said our money's in the bank?
We prefer stacking it in piles
and counting it by millions.
The Ardientes are being
protected by their wealth.
Taking that from them
will weaken their very core.
[tense music playing]
Where could they have hidden
their money within this mansion?
[Diego] Thanks.
[pensive music playing]
[soft music playing]
[phone rings]
Diego?
Ivy, how are you doing?
Uh…
I'm fine.
I'm at the Ardientes' mansion.
Uh, Diego…
Um…
Arnaldo just told me about this.
Now I'm wondering.
The Ardientes don't have their money
kept in a bank here or overseas.
Did you know that?
Why are you suddenly so interested?
What are you planning, Ivy?
You're in the home of murderers.
You have to be careful.
Like I said…
I can take care of myself.
I know where the guards are stationed…
and where the CCTV cameras are located.
I know how to get past them.
Thanks for checking up on me.
But it's getting late.
Ivy?
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Ivy?
Ivy!
[suspenseful music playing]
Ivy?
[tense music playing]
Ivy, it's me, Diego.
-Diego.
-Come here.
[tense music playing]
I knew it!
Hey, Ivy.
I'll find you, and I will catch you.
[line rings]
Hello? Ramirez.
Report to me immediately.
We need to catch someone. Hurry up.
[ominous music playing]
[Emilia] You thought
you could hide from me?
I will find you, Ivy.
[hums teasingly]
[ominous music playing]
Please protect
my daughter from our enemies.
Yes, ma'am?
Ramirez, what took you so long? Hurry!
Search every inch of that building.
Find Ivy Aguas.
-All right.
-Hurry up!
Hmm… I'm coming to get you.
[tense music playing]
[man] That way.
Jenny?
Ma'am?
Is that you, Jenny?
Jenny!
Seriously, Jenny?!
[Jenny] Ma'am, I'm sorry.
If you two want to hook up,
do it in your rooms!
You're disgusting, Fabian!
[Emilia] Unbelievable!
Ramirez, look for Ivy in the back.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Keep your eyes peeled!
Yes, ma'am.
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Emilia.
What are you doing there?
I'm looking for something.
[Raul] At this hour? Let's go back inside.
Come on.
It's late.
[mellow music playing]
Go on, Ivy. Go back to your room.
Diego, be careful.
I will. Go inside!
Thank you.
[mellow music playing]
[whispers] Go on.
Well, well, well… And another well.
Where have you been?
Why are you out of breath?
Wait. Who did you seduce this time?
A, the guards?
B, Madrigal?
Or letter C, Diego?
[dramatic music playing]
You know, Ivy…
you can't fool me.
Well, I'm not trying to fool you.
I just came from Arnaldo's room.
I couldn't help myself.
What?
If you don't want to believe me…
Um…
Oops.
[snickers]
Or do you want me to wake Arnaldo up so…
But, Emilia, your son's worn out.
Emilia…
My future mother-in-law,
let's stop fighting.
And I'm sorry for what
happened at dinner earlier.
I'm sorry, my future mother-in-law.
I don't want us to fight.
But…
[sighs] If you don't stop
breathing down my neck,
you know that…
I won't back down.
I'll take what little you still have left.
It won't just stress you out,
you might go into depression too.
[tense music playing]
[Diego] Arnaldo is the key
to finding where
they're keeping their money.
Proceed with the plan.
Julio Ardiente's head is mine.
I will kill him myself.
[Emilia] I have no patience
for Ivy, Aunt Claire.
I have to resort back to my old tricks.
[Claire] Like what you did to Camia Cruz?
Are you ready for your new assignment?
Yes, ma'am.
Ivy agreed to have dinner with you.
Are you excited for our dinner?
-Of course.
-I shall see you.
I'm very excited, Emilia.
[theme music playing]